... Three minutes.
Oui, Chef. Turn on the stove. Come on. Hurry up. Oui, Chef.
- Hurry! - Oui, Chef.
Alain? What did I say? What did I say?
Three distinct soils from three distinct local ecosystems.
That's what the Corporal asked for. That's what it's gotta look like.
You heard her? I need more.
Christ. Can't we just slip her some blinis?
If you want the Foundling Guard to play marimba on your gonads, yeah.
I can't keep on like this. Dressing like a peasant dishing out slop
whilst the goon squad does me a colonoscopy with their eyes.
Buck up, Malcolm. You might get fired by lunchtime.
Lift your arms.
- Oh, yes, it's tingling. - Yes.
- I can really feel that, actually. - It's supposed to be.
Yeah, it's lovely.
Hey!
What is this? It's not boiled.
You have shit in your ears?
I said boiled and salted. Take it back.
Come on, take it back, your fancy French bullshit.
This crunchy one has got a bit of... zing to it, hasn't it?
I... I know I'm a broken record but are you sure it's safe to eat?
It can't be nutritious.
It's very good for you. It's what we used to eat when we had nothing.
Yes, but we don't have nothing now, do we? We, in fact, have quite a lot of something.
That's exactly your problem, my friend.
- Your friend? I'm not your friend... - No...
Come on, Nicky. We trust Herbert's folk remedies, don't we?
They cured us of the wretched mold, after all.
We'll go over more cuts later, right?
Yes. The great culling of the fuckwit army.
Actually, on that point the staff is growing a bit jumpy
with the firings. Sorry. The contractions or whatever.
It... it's all a bit brutal.
It's good.
Not hugely terrific for morale, is it?
Well, sorry, Nicky but we can't have dead weight on the payroll, you know?
We need a lean operation. No baby fat.
And no leeches.
Lenny, I have those financials for you to review. The "thing."
What thing?
The thing. You know, my love.
The Belize fund.
No, later. Later, yeah?
Now, I have to make preparations for Daddy's birthday.
You can handle the cabinet meeting by yourself, can't you?
Sure.
- So are you going to tell me? - Tell you what?
Why you are dressed like an effete goatherder?
I have no idea what you mean.
Oh, my god, Victor.
Don't tell me you've gone rural to please him, hm?
Beg your pardon, certainly not.
Trying to dodge the boot, huh?
Why don't you go and show the Corporal your imported silk undies, too,
eh, Mr. Ploughman? See how he fancies those.
You look exceedingly well, Corporal.
I will be leading the meeting today.
I trust the Chancellor is well?
She's fine.
I see. Well, glad to hear it, Corporal.
Actually, we have a small gift for you, sir.
It's a bejeweled Frankish sword
in the style of what historians believe the Foundling himself would've had...
I don't need your fucking sword. Yes, of course.
So...
Chancellor Vernham asked me to read you this.
"Corporal Zubak and I have decided jointly on a package of reforms,
one that is pursuant to our policy of improving the lives of working families.
Greed and foreign money must be stricken from our national character.
And we shall introduce a new policy.
Large-scale transference of private property
from the landowning elite to the working classes.
We must enact these broad reforms as soon as possible."
I... I say well done, Corporal.
So, it's land reform, is it?
That's what I said.
So then you'll know of the risks involved in land reform?
Traditionally, economic slowdown, food scarcity?
You'll have brushed up on your South African history?
I said we are doing it.
Then we'll look into it once we have the Chancellor's go-ahead.
No, you already have it.
I just fucking read it to you. No, of course, of course. It just...
I just meant her official comp... compliance.
You will start planning it now because I told you to. You understand?
Yes, yes, of course. Certainly, sir. I'm... I'm sorry if I...
Remember what happened to Emil Bartos, hm?
- Yes, sir, but... - That was just the beginning.
Very well, Corporal. Thank you. We'll get started on everything.
Well, my friends all hail the Foundling's heir.
My loves from atop our proud mountain peaks
and over the fields of flowering sugar beets
we hear the song of our ancestors.
They beckon to us
calling us homeward to the values and traditions we once cherished.
And in their simple joy and wisdom
we discover the sacred and self-evident truth.
This beloved land must belong to you.
So, very soon I will deliver
what previous Chancellor Edward Keplinger failed to deliver.
A comprehensive program of land reform.
I will take back what the fiendish oligarchs stole from you
and eradicate rural poverty forever.
Never again shall your labor be forsaken.
Never again shall our dream be denied.
Cut it. Was that good?
Perfect. Was it? Are you sure?
- Perfect. - Wasn't too earnest?
Lovely, lovely, Ma'am.
We will need to discuss how we budget for this.
It could require dipping into the holding company.
No... We keep all that separate. Thank you, Mr. Singer. Herbert?
It's fucking great, right? Just like in our dream, remember?
Yes! No, yes. No, exactly like it.
Yes. Land reform. Chunky words. Exciting.
I'll spare a thought for the Americans. They'll be in fucking fits over this.
No, Elena. We don't think about them anymore, all right?
They are gone now. It's just us and our people right here.
No. No, of course. Only being puckish.
Ma'am.
Oh, here you are, my love.
They brought your tea. Shall I pour us some?
I've been thinking, Lenny.
It... it really punches through, land reform.
Yes, I think so.
Yeah, the... the Robin Hood of it all.
You do see the problem, don't you?
"The problem"?
You can't be Robin Hood and the king at the same time.
The holding company, Lenny.
I can do both.
Both? No, you can't give the country back
while continuing to stash half of it in your purse.
We skim a little cream off the top. It's fine.
It's more than a little cream, my love.
Surely she doesn't mean "reform"
in the most literal sense of changing the form of what is?
She doesn't care what she means.
She would bankrupt this country if that belligerent buffalo tells her to.
The plan was always to elevate him.
Elevate him, yes. Not turn him into Herbert the fucking Terrible.
It is because of him that our cobalt mines lie dormant.
Because of him, our GDP is shrinking like a sphincter.
He has made the American cash cow leave for greener pastures.
She'll lose interest. She always does.
What if this time, she doesn't?
I'm working on it.
Madam, as per your request, I've compiled a full report
on recent American media trends and intelligence chatter. And the dominant conversation,
of course continues to be Taiwan
with tensions escalating
the US State Department's attempting to engage China...
Oh, no, let's start with Europe, yeah?
Well, yes. Yes, of course.
Well, we've seen increased focus on Germany's troubled markets...
No, no. Closer to us.
Closer than Germany, Madam. Yes.
Well, the US continues to eye opportunities for investment
in the Faban Corridor.
Now, our assets in the region are monitoring...
But nothing on us, no? No fun crackle on...
Oh, god. Kansas frump?
You know, what's her name? Holt. Senator Holt.
Well, Madam, I would say the new isolationist policies
devised by Corporal Zubak and yourself appear to have succeeded.
You and your government figure minimally in American media of late.
It seems as though that they've moved on.
Which is what you wanted, of course.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Door.
Happy almost birthday, Daddy.
Christ, look at you. Painted up like a Dutch whore.
Here. These are dead. You're dead. Lots in common. Much to discuss.
Well, we've gone very rural here. You're going to hate it. Well, tough tits.
Oh, stop looking at me like that. I'm... I'm fine. I'm better than fine, actually.
I just... Well, I haven't been sleeping well, that's all.
And it happens to be a terrific idea, land reform.
Yeah. It's not weak or boring.
You're... you're wrong.
And just because it isn't big enough for you.
You and your Faban annexation pipe dreams.
Delusional.
This is the real world, Daddy. Grow up!
And you're wrong about Herbert, too.
Yeah.
I'm fully in control of that situation. Yes, I am.
What's the matter?
Do you feel threatened?
Because he's a real man?
And you're a dried-up old cricket with teensy little balls.
Oh, you're jealous? Is that it?
Is that why you're trying to drive me mad, like Mommy? Well, it won't work.
I am father-inoculated. I... I spit you out.
I refuse you. I reject you because you are fucking pathetic!
No, no. I'm sorry. Sorry. No, sorry. Just...
Let's just forget about it, shall we, please?
Yeah, I don't want to spoil your big day tomorrow, all right? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Daddy.
Warm up, Elena.
Come on! All right. God.
Shoulders back.
Come on, from the hips, from the hips. Here. Here.
What is it?
Nothing. I'm just...
I'm fine. I'm just a bit tired,
that's all.
A bit tired?
I was just...
talking to Daddy earlier and...
well, I just was thinking, is it...
is it right, land reform? Is it what we need?
No, it is. It... it...
Yes, you're right. I think it is, yes. I just...
I don't want the rope going slack, that's all. Just...
No, I... do think it will work.
Yes, I... I do like it.
No, what are you doing? God, what...
- Come here. - What?
Come here. Get on the floor!
- Come on, get down! Next to the vent! - My hand!
- You're hurting me! - Closer to the vent.
- No... - Come on, no. Right next to it. - No, no.
- No! - Right next to it! Come on, breathe.
- Come on, breathe your fuckin' poison! - I can't.
- Come on! - No, I can't!
I can't! I'm sorry.
I can't. I can't do it. I can't.
Elena, you cannot do it because you are not cured.
You are still sick in the head.
It's not inside these walls. It's inside you. Let it out.
- What? - Really let it out. Tell me everything.
What are you hiding? Tell me everything.
Oh, god. Everything?
Oh, well, fuck me. I don't know. Where would I begin?
It's everywhere. There's...
Right.
Slush funds in Belize State Bank, the holding company.
Fucking a billion or more in assets.
My name, Nicky's name, through our partners.
Thousands, thousands of fucking strings of... of money
purloined from local businesses, farms, pension funds.
Just... just shit I can't ever unravel.
It's just... I have made such a fucking mess. I'm sorry.
That hurts.
Poetry has always been the lifeblood of any thriving civil society
and with the blessed help of our government
these poetry centers shall be the fountains
from which our national spirit might quaff if I may say, poetically.
What is it?
What the fuck happened? She's all right.
- Well, Elena, what happened? - Oh, thank you, child. Look, I'm fine.
This is ridiculous. We were exercising, and I overdid it.
This is unacceptable, Corporal. You can't push her like this.
She hasn't been eating well.
She's been eating well for the first time in her life.
I'm... I'm fine. I just slipped.
It's that gym floor, Nicky. It's like a fucking dolphin's back.
Okay. Fetch Agnes. We're getting the Chancellor a proper dinner.
- No, you're not. - Now listen, Corporal
I've been very patient with your process these past few months
and I believe we've accommodated each other
with as little friction as can be expected under the circumstances.
But now my wife's health and happiness have been jeopardized.
No. She's happy, and she's healthy. The only one who is not is you.
I beg your pardon?
Oh, just stop it, you two!
If my energy is low it's because I'm not sleeping.
Not sleeping? You're a house cat on opium, darling.
She's not sleeping well.
It's true. It's your twitching, Nicky.
It's your hypnic jerks.
Well, how can I sleep with all that foot jiggling?
Well, why didn't you say so?
I'm sorry. It's just... Well, we had a little chat and...
perhaps you and I ought to try a night apart.
What do you mean?
I just need to regulate, Nicky.
I don't understand. Is this just for tonight?
Yeah, yeah. Just for tonight. Just a night. Or a... few.
- And this is your idea or his idea? - It's our idea.
It's Herbert's suggestion which I agree with.
Pardon me, Madam. How can I help? Hello, Agnes.
You would like to know how you can help?
Yes, Corporal, if you please. Yes, I do please.
I please to fuckin' hang you out that window by your ankles!
Oh, god.
What is it that's your concern, sir?
Elena nearly died sliding on that ice rink you call a gym.
Herbert, please, I...
No, it's all right, Madam.
Corporal, I can assure you that the gymnasium
and indeed every inch of this Palace
has been maintained to the standard to which it's always been maintained
which is to say, the very highest.
You harm her again we send you to the zoo as lion food.
Do you understand?
Yes, Corporal. Think we understand each other quite well.
Get out!
Oh, god. Out! Everyone, please. I just... I'm getting an early night.
All right, everyone, eyes up.
Eyes up. Good morning.
Madam and Corporal Zubak have asked that the menu for Joseph's birthday dinner
include "folk cuisine of thorough and rigorous nutrition."
My condolences to your whisks.
Three more minutes.
Come on, more. Come on!
Almost out of Oskar's pills.
Yeah, I can't.
Peter, I need them.
And if I deviate from the new medical regime
he'll have me in prison by suppertime.
- I'm sorry. - Go on.
And there we are. Or more like this probably?
No, right. Right a bit.
- No? No, no. Right... Or left? Oh, no... - Oh, stop it, oh, stop it!
- Only joking. - Just...
Is your wrist still hurting?
A bit.
Our friend Diazepam might do you good. Ease the pain.
No, Nicky. Herbert's given me a tincture thingy.
And that's working, is it?
Stop it.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
And who the fuck are all these people?
I thought it had to be a birthday party with real people
not some fancy fucks and fine China
so I took the liberty of inviting some of our people from the countryside.
It's a great opportunity.
Opportunity?
Yes, you know, to... to tell them.
Tell them what?
What you told me about the money.
Tell... tell them?
Yes, you don't have to tell details.
You just tell them you made mistakes
that you took from them, and clean your conscience.
No...
- No. I don't think  I'll be doing that. - Why not? Why not?
Well... D'you... It's...
D'you know it's not really that sort of occasion, hm? Is it?
No, it's... it's just more of a celebration. Yes, that's it.
- Elena... - Let's sit down there.
Welcome. I'm so thrilled you are all here
because you are the real people
and that's what my father would've wanted.
As for you, birthday boy 83 today.
Congratulations.
Daddy, you and I both know that you are still very much here with me.
And so happy birthday to Daddy and...
Many more
And I bless you all for joining us.
Hello, everyone.
I'm not really good at speeches, but...
my people had a toast.
"You may build it as tall as you want
but you build it from our earth!"
- Our earth! - Our earth!
Our earth, yes! And I would like to add...
Sorry. We would like to add
we are terribly sorry for everything that has been taken away from you.
Your toil, your hope, your money...
Happy birthday, Daddy.
Now, listen, I know I said some things yesterday that weren't...
weren't very kind
and I just... I...
- I just want... - Shut your fucking mouth.
- I'm sorry, I... - And stop apologizing, girl.
I wi... I wi... I will.
These hogs may call you Chancellor but I know who you really are.
Tell me who I really am.
A vapid, feckless, political whore with no principles.
A comic figure bereft of vision easily ruled.
All tits and no spine. Like your mother.
Yes. Yes, I... I kn... I know.
Oh, god. Can't you speak properly?
Well, don't... Stop saying that. I... I'm trying, Daddy.
You always just lie back and take it, don't you?
That's why the Americans loved you.
Are you going to take it from him?
He has you sucking his cock doesn't he?
Answer, you ugly bitch.
Pathetic.
Listen to me.
Be bold for once
in your hollow little life. Seize the mantle of history.
Yes. Yes, I'll try. I'll try, promise. Promise, Daddy.
I'm having a land reform planning meeting after this
so I will fill you in on everything later, yes?
I think I'll join the meeting today.
Agnes? Would you ask Mr. Laskin to let them know, please?
- Yes, Ma'am. - Thank you.
Well, here we go. Strap in, my fuckaneers.
I... I think I've come around, actually.
Well, yes, yes.
Yes, I think perhaps this might be a marvelous notion.
Oh, sure. Redistribute property. Tank the economy. Empty the grocers.
White Zimbabwe, here we come.
So, if one had a summer cottage at Lake Ober somethin' like that wouldn't be,
as it were "redistributed," would it?
Madam Chancellor, Corporal Zubak so glad you could both join us.
Indeed. We have prepared for you both
a planning precis regarding the rollout of what we'd like to call
the Vernham Agrarian Reform and Development Program.
So, if you'd like to take a glance
at the land reform planning packets in front of you
we thought we'd might like to start with, what?
Section One. Farm Expropriation.
Now, this has been adjusted to our current budget...
Minister Singer that's not where I'd like to start.
What? Oh, very well, Madam. Where would you like to start?
The land itself.
Right, in so far as?
Securing it.
"Securing it"?
Obviously, one needs to secure the land before reforming it.
Well, certainly, Madam and in terms of the actionable...
Priority one is to protect the security and autonomy of our people.
And a program of reunification with our Faban brothers
is the only way to ensure our sovereignty.
Reunification?
I think this might get some chatter
from our American friends, don't you think, Mr. Laskin?
Madam, I hope my report, my counsel, did not animate this.
Oh, no, no. Not at all.
Though I imagine your job is about to become quite interesting.
- What are we... - Still our plan, my love.
Taking back what's been stolen
which would be impossible
without reuniting with the Faban Corridor first.
Yes? Good?
Good. It's cleaner this way. And it's actually the only way. Yeah.
Madam, if you are indeed proposing an annexation of the Faban Corridor
I must ardently advise extreme caution.
Madam, no contingency plans exist.
We would be playing the invasion by ear.
No one knows how the NATO powers will react
and if the security forces in the Faban zone resist
it'll be a bloodbath.
Mr. Laskin no one is proposing an invasion.
No one.
This is an expression of peace and love towards our countrymen across the border.
- But, Madam... - Onwards, my friends.
So, let's aim to mobilize by... end of the week?
I think that sounds reasonable, yeah?
Oh, and Herbert we should send you out there.
Give you a new title. Something like... "Faban Freedom Captain."
Yeah, something like that. Something fun. Snappy.
Yeah? Good.
My loves at long last, we have arrived
at the sacred hour of our glorious dream realized.
Indeed, it appears a reckoning has finally arrived for all
who ever desired Faban
self-determination.
I have dispatched top aides
including newly appointed Faban Freedom Commander Herbert Zubak
to ensure that these ancestral lands are reclaimed with the utmost care.
Chancellor Vernham and her supporters
have vied for these 800 square miles
of ethnic mountain land for years.
Chancellor Vernham's regime has been careful to describe
the operation as a "lawful annexation."
Vernham's defiant turnabout...
But the shots we're seeing unmarked vehicles moving silently into Faban territory
are impossible to deny.
This is all the hallmarks of an occupation.
This isn't an occupation, my friends.
Even as I speak, the Faban Parliament is voting unanimously to approve this reunion.
A mere 12 days after Vernham entered the Faban Corridor illegally.
Sources say Faban legislators
have been forced at gunpoint
to unanimously approve annexation making it official.
The White House responded swiftly today calling the invasion
"a tragic assault on Faban self-determination
and a mockery of NATO peacekeeping efforts."
The developments in the Faban Corridor this week
underscore the importance of our transatlantic partnerships.
Chancellor Vernham calls this a reunification
but we know the truth.
She seized this land illegally
and there will be consequences.
Chancellor Vernham's long-held dream of regaining control of the Faban Corridor
has finally been realized.
Most would agree that a reunion with our Faban brothers and sisters
is a cause for celebration.
But what will be the long-term effects on our...
Sit...
Nice to see you all. Good morning.
Madam Chancellor, does last week's military operation in the Faban...
"Military operation"? No.
Let's not use these words, "military operation."
No, not a single shot has been fired in the Faban Corridor
and there have been no casualties.
Madam Chancellor, to what extent does this reunion violate international agreements?
The agreements to which you refer are archaic and, therefore, not legal.
All we are doing is realizing our dream.
Our dream of a new Europe without limits, without cruelty.
And I assure you our actions are in full compliance with the law.
- Who's next? - Madam Chancellor?
Yeah.
Have you thought through all the possible risks?
Economic sanctions, a possible visa ban?
Did you ask the United States if they thought through the possible risks of their exploits
in Afghanistan, Iraq Yemen, Libya, Indonesia, Central America
every corner of the world?
Actions which were carried out at great human cost
with no resulting UN sanctions whatsoever.
Did you ask them about that, did you? No, I didn't think you did.
- Madam, the stock market - Yeah.
has declined sharply and exchange rates have hit record lows. Yeah, money likes quiet, you know?
Right now, there is noise.
Our erstwhile friends across the Atlantic are responsible for that noise.
But once they settle down, the markets will too.
- Yes, but... - Yeah, this is no longer a conversation.
Let me finish. Friends
there are times when one must choose the hardest road.
I have chosen that road and I have done so
in the name of liberty. Thank you.
Chancellor?
What have we here?
I present you a cornerstone of the Monastery of the Holy Trinity.
It's the ancient spiritual home of our brothers in the Faban lands.
Simple peasants once fought to get this relic back
from the land that it leaves.
Like in our dream, Elena.
Well, that's... that's lovely.
Thank you.
Elena, as soon as we can we should start on the rest.
"The rest"?
Yes, of our dream. Land reform.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, of course. No, we must give land reform the best chance of success.
- When? - When the Faban turbulence is behind us.
Our budget has shifted now
and significant aid will need to be sent to the Faban Corridor.
And the rest of our funds, we ought to set aside in case of any repercussions.
So, when will our dream come true?
This is our dream.
The remainder of which we'll budget for next year.
Or the year after. Year after?
We can't afford to be careless, Herbert. Land reform is simply too important.
Bloody hell.
What the fuck do you want?
I've been instructed to bring you this. What is it?
These are the clothes she wants you to wear for the banquet tonight.
Isn't that lovely for the Faban victory party. I'm not wearing this Nutcracker shit.
She requested that you do, Corporal.
Stop calling me that.
Do you want me to help you?
It's all right. I've got some spare undershirts in there for you.
Why are you being nice to me? It's stupid.
Well, I'm just doin' me job, my stupid job.
Hail the conquering hero.
Sure.
You're smiling.
The entire Western world is about to pig fuck us with sanctions
and you're smiling.
Now, look, I say you're stressed
but you must admit, our plan to sideline the Corporal has worked.
The plan, sir, was to get back to business as usual.
This is emphatically not business as usual.
I suppose my head knows that's true
yet I must confess, my heart feels oddly tickled.
I think you'll find the imminent demise of our economy
slightly outweighs the benefits to your love life, sir.
You don't think we could ride out those sanctions somehow
with our new plan C?
Oh, yes. China.
A cold, heartless superpower that's going to sort out all our problems.
Think happy thoughts, Laskin. It's time to twist the night away.
I love the outfit, Corporal.
Just remember, if you're feeling unwell
just come and find me, all right? Come and find me.
Smile, darling.
All right, did you write a speech?
What is he doing here? Cheers, my love.
Good evening!
Good evening...
and welcome, welcome one and all to the Heroes' Banquet!
Tonight, we celebrate our returning heroes
and our joyous reunification with our Faban brothers!
And so the question is are you ready to party?
Yes!
I'd keep an eye on that Bordeaux by the way, Madam.
NATO might snatch that back by the intermission.
And haven't you all scrubbed up well? Don't ya all look great?
What do we have down here? It's Emil Bartos
and he seems to be chaperoning his granddaughter.
And how old is she, if I may inquire?
She looks like she'd be just as happy with a ice cream and a pony ride.
But let's imagine how poor, dear, old Keplinger is feeling right now.
And you know he's gonna be watchin' this, folks.
You know he's watching this up there in his mansion in the mountains
weeping into his chardonnay.
Well, Mr. Former Chancellor of course you hate reunification.
We knew that after your first two divorces.
But, my friends, let's consider for a second
what's happening in this very country outside these four walls now.
A pointless, needless, wasteful, expensive undertaking
that's gonna drag on for years and years and years.
I'm speaking, of course about the national poetry centers.
Oh, dear, oh, dear. Mr. Vernham's not looking happy with that one. Mr. Vernham's not looking happy...
- Now, that was rather tame. Come on. - If you don't like the material
maybe you could write a poem about it.
Madam Chancellor? Mr. Bartos would like to discuss the China brief.
La... later.
Paging Dr. Freud. Chancellor's husband. It's very clear who wears the trousers...
What the fuck is the China brief?
I imagine it's where China is discussed briefly.
Give us a cheer if you're Special Forces! The Air Force! The Security Service!
Now, Nicholas, I have a submission for you.
I don't know if you're still taking submissions... Go for it! Go!
...but my literary assistant will bring it.
Thank you, precious.
It goes something like this.
"There once was a man so astounding
whose job was so very confounding.
He lived at the Palace
and tugged on his phallus
and shouted 'My granddad's the Foundling!'"
Oskar! All right. It's okay. Deep breaths. Deep...
- Fuck off. - I'm trying to help!
You had your chance to help.
You're all right. Mom's here.
It is not a scoff. It's a joke!
All a big joke.
Yeah, a joke.
Don't forget tomorrow. The bankers, the zoo.
Yes, yes.
- See you tomorrow. - See you tomorrow. Good night.
Well, I did enjoy it.
It was patchy, you know.
Comedy is like that. Absolutely no one's good at it.
You look tired.
- Are you tired? - No.
Bit cranky?
Okay.
- You sure? - Yes, I'm sure.
Well, I'm not sure I believe you, but... Whatever. Long night.
What is that? Have you always done that? Done what?
- That sniff. You do a sniff now. - A what?
Well, you know, a little...
I do?
You're not aware of it?
No.
How can you not be aware of it?
I don't know.
You're not aware there's something you do many times a day
that you never used to do?
I don't think I do a sniff, no.
But you do. I just told you that you do.
Does it bother you?
No. No, doesn't bother me.
Maybe a bit irritating that you won't acknowledge that you do it.
Ah, you find me irritating? No, that's not what I said.
Well, it's how you seem with me. It's how I seem,
is it? When?
Tonight. Now.
I was barely aware of you tonight.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Because I was celebrating my country and our people.
Must my attention always be on you?
Why are you meeting with Bartos?
I might not be.
Answer me.
Why are you meeting with Bartos?
Because he's free to practice business
and his business is of consequence to my country.
No, this man is of no consequence to us. None whatsoever.
Well, you know, just a check-in. Check-in on what?
Stuff. Few things.
China?
Maybe, perhaps, an option.
A free-trade deal with the largest nation on Earth who oppose our enemies.
Is that... is that a crime?
"You may build it as tall as you like but you build it from our earth."
Oh, sweet.
That something your mommy would sing in the beet fields?
No, Elena. Look at me. It's our dream.
Your dream.
- What? - Your dream, not mine.
I don't fucking dream.
Oh, god, is that so shocking?
Jesus Christ. Fucking grow up.
Maybe I occasionally dream but I don't remember them.
I do.
Yes, you do. Your dreams come from the mind of a child.
You're not enormously bright, are you?
Excuse me?
Big baby ox man.
Your father always knew that you are weak.
Poor baby ox.
You steal money from poor people
you hide it and you turn your soul to shit.
I bet you dream about fucking me, don't you?
Yes, you do.
You dream about fucking me.
But I don't dream about fucking you.
I thought you were fun. You used to be fun.
You're boring now.
You don't deny it.
What?
That you dream about fucking me?
you do not have a graceful mind.
Keep sputtering, ox.
Don't call me fucking ox!
I'm not an ox, you hear me? Look at me. I'm not a fucking ox!
No, you're a butcher.
Fuck!
Thank you, Agnes.
There is one thing I'd like to speak with you about, Ma'am.
Yes, what is it?
The folk remedies prescribed by the former Chief of Health and Safety
have not been working
and Oskar has been having seizures again.
What? Agnes! Why was I not told?
I'm sorry. I mean, I wanted to be honest with you now.
Well, I'm glad you're honest with me.
Mother to mother.
Yes, of course. We must resume Oskar's prior treatment immediately.
Thank you... That means... I can't tell you how much that means.
But...
co-parenting is about honesty
and for you to have withheld information about Oskar's condition
well, it doesn't make me feel like we're operating in good faith, Agnes.
Yes, I think, the best thing for Oskar
would be for him to stay here with me so I can supervise his treatment.
Because I... I really can't trust you right now, Agnes.
That's so disappointing. I'm sure you understand.
Yes, I...
- Thank you. - I...
That's all.